<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ECDAR</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on ECDAR</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:45:55 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Architecture</title><link>/architecture/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/architecture/</guid><description>This page describes the Ecdar tool architecture as of spring 2022.
The general design intent of having two verification engines, is that it should make the whole platform more reliable. j-Ecdar The intention of j-Ecdar is to be a form of reference implementation, where no effort is put into optimizing the code for speed, but rather for Correctness Readability Reveaal The intention of the Reveaal engine is to get a verification engine that is fast and parallelizable.</description></item><item><title>Developers</title><link>/developers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/developers/</guid><description>Developers that have contributed to the project over time
Florian Lorber Ulrik Nyman Niels Frederik Sinding Vistisen Nicklas Hjortshøj Hugøy Sebastian Lund Thorulf Neustrup First version og j-Ecdar: Master thesis 2018-2019
Andrej Kiviriga Napalys Klicius Cristina Ioana Simionescu First version of the Ecdar GUI (based on H-Uppaal) Pre-Master thesis 2017 Master thesis 2018 (Simulator) Master thesis 2018 (Fault localisation)
Casper Møller Bartholomæussen Tobias Rosenkrantz Gundersen Rene Mejer Lauritsen Christian Ovesen First version of the GUI code-base known as H-Uppaal Master thesis 2016-2017</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>/history/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/history/</guid><description>This is a short outline of the history of the development of the different parts of the Ecdar tools.
Ecdar stands for Environment for Compositional Design and Analysis of Real Time Systems. Uppaal TIGA versions - 2010 - 2013 The first version of the tool (0.6 to 0.10) was based on the GUI and verification engine of Uppaal TIGA. Efter this it was released as part of Uppaal TIGA in version 0.</description></item></channel></rss>